<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Chi-Kuang Yeh/葉啓光</title>
    <link>https://chikuang.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Chi-Kuang Yeh/葉啓光</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:58:10 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://chikuang.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sample Resource Post</title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/sample-resource/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/sample-resource/</guid>
      <description>Sample Resource Post This is a sample resource post that demonstrates how to add individual resource posts to your website.&#xA;What you can include: Code examples: Share code snippets and complete scripts Tutorials: Step-by-step guides for various topics Data sets: Links to useful data sets for analysis Tools and software: Reviews and recommendations Research materials: Notes, papers, and other academic resources Example Code Block # Sample R code library(ggplot2) data &amp;lt;- data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R Markdown Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/real-resource/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/real-resource/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown Cheat Sheet This post provides a quick reference for R Markdown syntax, including:&#xA;Headers and formatting Code chunks Inline code Tables and lists Links and images Example: Code Chunk # This is an R code chunk summary(cars) Useful Links R Markdown: The Definitive Guide RStudio Cheat Sheets Feel free to download the PDF version or view the source code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/post/chi-kuang_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/post/chi-kuang_projects/</guid>
      <description>Back to main site&#xA;This is an example page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/readme/</guid>
      <description>Resources Page Guide This directory contains your resource posts and materials. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to use it:&#xA;Adding Resource Posts Create a new markdown file in this directory (e.g., my-resource.md) Use the following front matter: --- title: &amp;#34;Your Resource Title&amp;#34; date: 2025-01-20 description: &amp;#34;Brief description of the resource&amp;#34; tags: [&amp;#34;tag1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;tag2&amp;#34;] categories: [&amp;#34;resources&amp;#34;] --- Write your content in markdown format Add any files (PDFs, code, etc.) to the static/ directory Types of Resources You Can Add Tutorials: Step-by-step guides Code examples: Scripts and code snippets Data sets: Links to useful data Tools and software: Reviews and recommendations Research materials: Notes, papers, presentations Course materials: Lecture notes, assignments Documentation: How-to guides and manuals File Organization Keep related files in organized subdirectories Use descriptive filenames Include proper metadata in front matter Link to external resources when appropriate Example Structure content/resources/ ├── _index.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
