<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on Chi-Kuang Yeh/葉啓光</title>
    <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on Chi-Kuang Yeh/葉啓光</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://chikuang.github.io/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Job Market reflection</title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/yeh_ttap_reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/yeh_ttap_reflection/</guid>
      <description>This is just a self-reflection of the job market process for tenure-track statistics/biostatistics professorship in North America of the academic year 2024–2025. I am adding more details as I go through the process. I hope this can help other job seekers in the future, especially for the ones coming from Canada and do not have any connections or experiences in the US.&#xA;Profile Identity I am a Taiwanese-Canadian, and do not have the US passport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Regression Design</title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/opt_design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/opt_design/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Optimal Regression Design In statistical modeling, especially in regression analysis, we often face the question:&#xA;“Where and how should we collect data to obtain the most accurate parameter estimates?”&#xA;This question is answered by Optimal Experimental Design, a field that seeks to identify the best sampling scheme under a specified statistical model.&#xA;🎯 General Objective Let the model be a linear regression:&#xA;\[ Y_i = g(x_i;\boldsymbol{\beta}) + \varepsilon_i,\quad \varepsilon_i \sim \mathcal{N}(0, \sigma^2) \] where:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFCF computing resource shortguide</title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/uw_mfcf_computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/uw_mfcf_computing/</guid>
      <description>Only read if you wanna use school server&#xA;Which Operating System do you use? In all OS, you can use Terminal or cmd to connect, but I perfer not using it as a beginner. Windows, depends on the version of your OS… but I strongly recommend using WSL2. Otherwise, you may use Putty. In addition, I think MobaXterm is a good choice to connect to the servers. MacOS, well… you may just use terminal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chikuang.github.io/resources/readme/</guid>
      <description>Resources Page Guide This directory contains your resource posts and materials. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to use it:&#xA;Adding Resource Posts Create a new markdown file in this directory (e.g., my-resource.md) Use the following front matter: --- title: &amp;#34;Your Resource Title&amp;#34; date: 2025-01-20 description: &amp;#34;Brief description of the resource&amp;#34; tags: [&amp;#34;tag1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;tag2&amp;#34;] categories: [&amp;#34;resources&amp;#34;] --- Write your content in markdown format Add any files (PDFs, code, etc.) to the static/ directory Types of Resources You Can Add Tutorials: Step-by-step guides Code examples: Scripts and code snippets Data sets: Links to useful data Tools and software: Reviews and recommendations Research materials: Notes, papers, presentations Course materials: Lecture notes, assignments Documentation: How-to guides and manuals File Organization Keep related files in organized subdirectories Use descriptive filenames Include proper metadata in front matter Link to external resources when appropriate Example Structure content/resources/ ├── _index.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
